<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="help">
    <![CDATA[
<h2>&nbsp;What&apos;s Spudoku?</h2>
<p>
Spudoku is sudoku with colors.
</p>
<p>
You can use Spudoku to create puzzles (with solutions) that you can
solve on a ColorKu board from Mad Cave Bird Games.  Or you can solve
the puzzles right here on your device.
</p>

<h2>&nbsp;Create a puzzle</h2>
<p>
Use the spinners to select a <i>difficulty</i> and a <i>layout</i>,
which is the arrangement of colors that are already set as part of the puzzle.
</p>
<p>
Then touch the <i>New</i> button and Spudoku will make you a puzzle never
before seen&mdash;by anyone!
</p>
<p>
Some combinations of difficulty and layout may be imposssible to
create a puzzle for, such as a <i>Wicked</i> puzzle with the
<i>Identical Squares</i> layout.  If puzzle creation is taking too
long just press the <i>Cancel</i> button and ask it to make something
more possible.
</p>

<h2>&nbsp;Use the buttons</h2>
<p>
Touch the <i>Puzzle</i> button to temporarily remove any colors
you&apos;ve placed and show only the original puzzle colors.
</p>
<p>
Touch the <i>Solution</i> button to show the solution.
</p>
<p>
Touch either button again to return to your work-in-progress.
</p>
<p>
Hold the <i>Puzzle</i> button to reset the puzzle to its original state.
</p>

<h2>&nbsp;Solve the puzzle</h2>
<p>
Place colors by dragging them from the row of colored circles and
dropping them into place on the board.
</p>
<p>
Remove them by flicking them off the board.
</p>
<p>
If you&apos;ve placed a color you&apos;re not sure about, tap it to mark it
with a question mark as a reminder you&apos;re not sure about it.  Tap it again
to remove the question mark.
</p>

<h2>&nbsp;Get hints</h2>
<p>
Got stuck somewhere?  Touch the <i>Hint</i> button and Spudoku will
give you a hint to help you place the next color.
</p>

<h2>&nbsp;Training wheels</h2>
<p>
Turn on <i>Training wheels</i> to prevent you from putting a color in
the wrong place.  If you drag a color to a place it doesn&apos;t belong
it will just go back to the row of colors.
</p>
<p>
You can turn off <i>training wheels</i> at any time but you can only
turn them on if you haven&apos;t placed any colors on the puzzle yet
because they may be wrong.
</p>

<h2>&nbsp;How do you pronounce Spudoku?</h2>
<p>
The same way you do.
</p>
    ]]>
  </string>
</resources>
